<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports News Archives - MX Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/category/sports-news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/category/sports-news/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:24:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mx.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mx-onnline.png</url>
	<title>Sports News Archives - MX Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/category/sports-news/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fucsovics upsets Fritz in Stuttgart; Tiafoe reaches semifinals</title>
		<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/fucsovics-upsets-fritz-in-stuttgart-tiafoe-reaches-semifinals/</link>
					<comments>https://mx.online.mills.edu/fucsovics-upsets-fritz-in-stuttgart-tiafoe-reaches-semifinals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mx.online.mills.edu/?p=1261</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fritz, the top-ranked American men’s player at No. 8, was on the back foot immediately after losing serve in the opening game before the rest of the first set went with serve. The second was even at 5-5 until Fucsovics broke Fritz and closed out the win on his fourth match point in the next ... <a title="Fucsovics upsets Fritz in Stuttgart; Tiafoe reaches semifinals" class="read-more" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/fucsovics-upsets-fritz-in-stuttgart-tiafoe-reaches-semifinals/" aria-label="More on Fucsovics upsets Fritz in Stuttgart; Tiafoe reaches semifinals">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/fucsovics-upsets-fritz-in-stuttgart-tiafoe-reaches-semifinals/">Fucsovics upsets Fritz in Stuttgart; Tiafoe reaches semifinals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Fritz, the top-ranked American men’s player at No. 8, was on the back foot immediately after losing serve in the opening game before the rest of the first set went with serve. The second was even at 5-5 until Fucsovics broke Fritz and closed out the win on his fourth match point in the next game.</p>



<p>Fritz would have faced his friend Tiafoe in the semifinals. Instead, that opportunity goes to Fucsovics. It’s the Hungarian’s first semifinal on tour since 2021 on any surface, and his first ever on grass despite having been the Wimbledon boys champion in 2010.</p>



<p>“I was a very talented boy,” the 31-year-old Fucsovics said. “Throughout my career I always believed I can play good tennis on grass. Maybe it was because of the Wimbledon title.”</p>



<p>The third-seeded Tiafoe is the highest-ranked player left in the draw after he beat Lorenzo Musetti 6-7 (6), 7-6 (4), 6-2.</p>



<p>It’s the first grass-court semifinal for Tiafoe, who lost both of his previous career quarterfinals on the surface.</p>



<p>There was an unusual moment when, at 3-2 up in the second, he hit a drop shot which landed with so much backspin that it bounced back over the net to his side, winning the point.</p>



<p>Home favorite Jan-Lennard Struff defeated French veteran Richard Gasquet 6-4, 7-5 in the last quarterfinal for a semifinal meeting with fourth-seeded Hubert Hurkacz, who defeated Australia’s Christopher O’Connell 6-4, 6-4.</p>



<p>Buoyed by raucous support from Stuttgart supporters, Struff hit 18 aces to beat Gasquet for the first time at the third attempt. Gasquet won their previous meetings in 2016 and 2018.</p>



<p>The French player, who turns 37 on Sunday, upset top-seeded Stefanos Tsitsipas for his 600th ATP Tour win on Thursday but was unable to reproduce that form against Struff. The German goes on to his 11th semifinal as he bids for his first career win.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/fucsovics-upsets-fritz-in-stuttgart-tiafoe-reaches-semifinals/">Fucsovics upsets Fritz in Stuttgart; Tiafoe reaches semifinals</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mx.online.mills.edu/fucsovics-upsets-fritz-in-stuttgart-tiafoe-reaches-semifinals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Suns, Kyle Kuzma Rumors Heating Up</title>
		<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/suns-kyle-kuzma-rumors-heating-up/</link>
					<comments>https://mx.online.mills.edu/suns-kyle-kuzma-rumors-heating-up/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mx.online.mills.edu/?p=1258</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Phoenix Suns and Kyle Kuzma have again been connected. It&#8217;s that time of year where rumors begin to run wild, though a recent spark between the Phoenix Suns and Washington Wizards forward Kyle Kuzma appears to be more than just whispers.  Recently, ClutchPoints&#8217; Brett Siegel reported the Suns have again been linked with Kuzma, who is expected ... <a title="Suns, Kyle Kuzma Rumors Heating Up" class="read-more" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/suns-kyle-kuzma-rumors-heating-up/" aria-label="More on Suns, Kyle Kuzma Rumors Heating Up">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/suns-kyle-kuzma-rumors-heating-up/">Suns, Kyle Kuzma Rumors Heating Up</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Phoenix Suns and Kyle Kuzma have again been connected.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s that time of year where rumors begin to run wild, though a recent spark between the Phoenix Suns and Washington Wizards forward Kyle Kuzma appears to be more than just whispers. </p>



<p>Recently, ClutchPoints&#8217; Brett Siegel reported the Suns have again been linked with Kuzma, who is expected to opt out of his player option and become a free agent. </p>



<p>&#8220;There is a real belief that the Wizards will move Beal in attempts to start over and build for the future, which is why the notion of Kuzma following him out the door in Washington is relevant,&#8221; said Siegel. &#8220;Should this happen, the 27-year-old forward will become one of the better names available in free agency. Multiple league sources who spoke with ClutchPoints recently claimed the Phoenix Suns would be a prime landing spot for him.&#8221;</p>



<p>Kuzma had been a name connected with the Suns in the build up to the trade deadline, though it was ultimately Kevin Durant that landed in the desert after new owner Mat Ishbia took over. &#8220;</p>



<p>The Suns held interest in Kuzma ahead of the trade deadline this past season, according to The Athletic&#8217;s Shams Charania, and sources say they had reached out to the Wizards in attempts to discuss trades centered around the former first-round pick before they made a move on superstar Kevin Durant,&#8221; continued Siegel. </p>



<p>&#8220;Ultimately, discussions centered on Kuzma did not go anywhere, as Washington was unwilling to move him.&#8221;</p>



<p>Now, the possibility of adding Kuzma looks more legitimate. However, Phoenix will still need to resolve the futures of Chris Paul and Deandre Ayton before making any solidified splashes in free agency or the trade market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/suns-kyle-kuzma-rumors-heating-up/">Suns, Kyle Kuzma Rumors Heating Up</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mx.online.mills.edu/suns-kyle-kuzma-rumors-heating-up/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Will Chancellor Carol Christ&#8217;s Resignation Affect Cal Sports?</title>
		<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/how-will-chancellor-carol-christs-resignation-affect-cal-sports/</link>
					<comments>https://mx.online.mills.edu/how-will-chancellor-carol-christs-resignation-affect-cal-sports/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mx.online.mills.edu/?p=1255</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>She will leave Cal the same time that USC and UCLA leave the Pac-12. It&#8217;s a pivotal time for Golden Bears athleticsCal chancellor Carol Christ’s resignation announcement comes at a pivotal time in Cal athletics, and her successor will have a lot on his plate in determining Cal’s athletic future. Past chancellors have had a major influence ... <a title="How Will Chancellor Carol Christ&#8217;s Resignation Affect Cal Sports?" class="read-more" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/how-will-chancellor-carol-christs-resignation-affect-cal-sports/" aria-label="More on How Will Chancellor Carol Christ&#8217;s Resignation Affect Cal Sports?">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/how-will-chancellor-carol-christs-resignation-affect-cal-sports/">How Will Chancellor Carol Christ&#8217;s Resignation Affect Cal Sports?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>She will leave Cal the same time that USC and UCLA leave the Pac-12. It&#8217;s a pivotal time for Golden Bears athletics<br>Cal chancellor Carol Christ’s <strong>resignation announcement </strong>comes at a pivotal time in Cal athletics, and her successor will have a lot on his plate in determining Cal’s athletic future.</p>



<p>Past chancellors have had a major influence on the status of Cal sports in terms of goals, direction, philosophy and support. The chancellor’s view on the place of sports at the University of California, Berkeley, has, over the years, had a direct effect on wins and losses, particularly in revenue-producing sports.</p>



<p>The most noticeable influences come in determining admission requirements for incoming Cal athletes, and the financial support the university is willing to provide to the athletic department. But there are a number of subtle ways chancellors affect university sports, including the priority he/she establishes for Cal success in given sports. Those priorities become apparent in the words and actions of the chancellor.</p>



<p>Christ made her announcement on Thursday, saying she will <strong>step down at the end of the 2023-24 school year </strong>after taking over in 2017. Her departure will come at the same time that USC and UCLA will leave the Pac-12 for the Big Ten, giving the Pac-12 (or Pac-10, or whatever form the conference takes) an uncertain future. Presumably by that time, the Pac-12 will have a media-rights agreement with networks (that is expected to come in a month or two) that will indicate the TV income the remaining schools can expect. Also by that time, the conference may have determined whether it will become a 10-team conference or add one of two schools (San Diego State and SMU?) to remain a 12-team conference.</p>



<p>In any case the very existence of the Pac-12 conference is at stake, and it’s possible &#8212; though unlikely &#8212; the Pac-12 may not exist within a few years. Or if it does exist it might be in a very different configuration in the rapidly changing world of super conferences. Cal might have to decide just what it wants to be in the college sports landscape: Will it want to invest the kind of money it may take in the future to remain relevant at the top level of college sports? Or will it decide that it is just not worth it, and fall back to an Ivy League-style model, acknowledging that it can no longer compete at the highest level if it wants to maintain its high academic standing and integrity.</p>



<p>The Pac-12&#8217;s university presidents and chancellors make the final decision on any significant moves the conference makes. Their votes dictate change or lack of change.</p>



<p>Christ has generally been supportive of Cal athletics, diverting university funds to help minimize the large debt the sports department has incurred while supporting 28 sports. Her mere attendance of Cal sports events as well as her words provided the sense that she cared about sports at Cal.</p>



<p>“You can pretend like you care, but you can’t fake showing up,” former Cal women’s basketball coach Lindsay Gottlieb <strong>told the San Francisco Chronicle in 2018.</strong> “As someone who watches other leaders and tries to learn, she’s someone I’ve taken interest in. If there’s some sort of report card on her first year and a half that asks about her commitment to excellence in athletics, she’s off the charts.</p>



<p>“She’s committed to the issues surrounding athletics, to being successful and to everything at Cal being at a high level. I’ve been wildly impressed.”</p>



<p>That has not been the case for every Cal chancellor, and it is usually reflected in success on the field or on the court.</p>



<p>How her successor will view the importance of sports success remains to be seen. In large part it will depend on what the selection committee is looking for and how much that panel values elite-level sports.</p>



<p>The other major factor the next chancellor will determine is the future of athletic director Jim Knowlton. He has come under fire from some alumni, especially the way he dealt with the complaints directed at former women’s swimming and diving coach Teri McKeever, who has since been fired. It reportedly resulted in an internal investigation of Knowlton’s handling of that situation.</p>



<p>The athletic director obviously has a major influence on the success of the school’s athletic programs, and the Bears have not performed well in recent years in the three potential revenue sports – football and men’s and women’s basketball. Knowlton&#8217;s hiring of Mark Madsen as the new basketball coach has sparked optimism, though.</p>



<p>In general, a Cal chancellor will signify the school’s philosophy about its athletics programs with his/her words and actions. The background of the next chancellor may determine where Cal sports are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/how-will-chancellor-carol-christs-resignation-affect-cal-sports/">How Will Chancellor Carol Christ&#8217;s Resignation Affect Cal Sports?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mx.online.mills.edu/how-will-chancellor-carol-christs-resignation-affect-cal-sports/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bears Camp Access Limited for Fans</title>
		<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/bears-camp-access-limited-for-fans/</link>
					<comments>https://mx.online.mills.edu/bears-camp-access-limited-for-fans/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mx.online.mills.edu/?p=1252</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There will be only nine practices open to the general public at this year&#8217;s Bears training camp, starting with the July 27 session. The Bears report for training camp July 25 and begin practices the next day, with the first practice open to the public at Halas Hall on Thursday, July 27. The team announced ... <a title="Bears Camp Access Limited for Fans" class="read-more" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/bears-camp-access-limited-for-fans/" aria-label="More on Bears Camp Access Limited for Fans">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/bears-camp-access-limited-for-fans/">Bears Camp Access Limited for Fans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There will be only nine practices open to the general public at this year&#8217;s Bears training camp, starting with the July 27 session.</p>



<p>The Bears report for training camp July 25 and begin practices the next day, with the first practice open to the public at Halas Hall on Thursday, July 27.</p>



<p>The team announced its training camp schedule and ticket availability for fans on Friday and only nine practices are available at Halas Hall for the general public. It&#8217;s the fewest post-pandemic practices they&#8217;ve had open to the general public at Halas Hall since moving training camp back to their home facility from Bourbonnanis starting with the 2020 training camp.</p>



<p>There is also the Sunday, Aug. 6 Meijer Bears Family Fest practice at Soldier Field Aug. 6 at 10:35 a.m. besides the nine practices at Halas Hall.</p>



<p>Part of the reason for fewer public practices than last year is they are taking the show on the road to practice at Indianapolis against the Colts Aug. 16 and 17 prior to the Aug. 19 preseason game at Indianapolis.</p>



<p>All Halas Hall practices begin at 10 a.m. The open practices are July 27, 28, 29, 31, Aug. 1, 4, 8, 9 and 10.</p>



<p>Practices at Halas Hall July 26, Aug. 2, 5 and 14 are closed to the general public but are open for special &#8220;community invite day&#8221; groups.</p>



<p>Tickets to practices are available at <strong><u><em>chicagobears.com/camp</em></u></strong> and are free. Disbursement of camp tickets will begin through <strong><em><u>chicagobears.com/camp</u></em></strong> at 10 a.m. on July 6. All tickets are distributed as mobile tickets and fans are limited to only four per practice.</p>



<p>Information on tickets for the Aug. 6 family day practice at Soldier Field will be put out at a later date. There is a charge for those tickets.</p>



<p>There is no parking at Halas Hall for fans. Parking is at Hawthorn Mall in Vernon Hills and transportation is provided for fans via shuttle.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="bears-training-camp-schedule">Bears Training Camp Schedule</h3>



<ul>
<li>Tuesday, July 25: Players report</li>



<li>Wednesday, July 26: 10 a.m. practice (open only to community invite day fans)</li>



<li>Thursday, July 27: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Friday, July 28: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Saturday, July 29: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Sunday, July 30: OFF DAY</li>



<li>Monday, July 31: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Tuesday, August 1: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Wednesday, Aug. 2: 10 a.m. practice (open only to community invite day fans)</li>



<li>Thursday, Aug. 3: OFF DAY</li>



<li>Friday, Aug. 4: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Saturday, Aug. 5: 10 a.m. practice (open only to community invite day fans)</li>



<li>Sunday, Aug. 6: 10:35 a.m. practice at Soldier Field, Miejer Family Fest (ticket information available at later date)</li>



<li>Monday, Aug. 7 OFF DAY</li>



<li>Tuesday, Aug. 8: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Wednesday, Aug. 9: 10 a.m. practice, open to general public</li>



<li>Thursday, Aug. 10: 10 a.m. final practice open to general public</li>



<li>Friday, Aug. 11: OFF DAY</li>



<li>Saturday, Aug. 12: Tennessee Titans at Bears preseason game No. 1, Soldier Field, noon</li>



<li>Sunday, Aug. 13: OFF DAY</li>



<li>Monday, Aug. 14: 10 a.m. practice (open only to community invite day fans)</li>



<li>Tuesday, Aug. 15: OFF DAY</li>



<li>Wednesday, Aug. 16: Time TBA, Bears practice at Indianapolis with Colts</li>



<li>Thursday, Aug. 17: Time TBA, Bears practice at Indianapolis with Colts</li>



<li>Friday, Aug. 18: OFF DAY</li>



<li>Saturday, Aug. 19: Bears at Indianapolis Colts, preseason game No. 2, 6 p.m.</li>



<li>Sunday, Aug. 20: OFF DAY</li>



<li>(All Practices closed to the public beginning Aug. 21)</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/bears-camp-access-limited-for-fans/">Bears Camp Access Limited for Fans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mx.online.mills.edu/bears-camp-access-limited-for-fans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Antonio Lopez Habas joins Mohun Bagan as Technical Director</title>
		<link>https://mx.online.mills.edu/antonio-lopez-habas-joins-mohun-bagan-as-technical-director/</link>
					<comments>https://mx.online.mills.edu/antonio-lopez-habas-joins-mohun-bagan-as-technical-director/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mx.online.mills.edu/?p=1249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mohun Bagan Super Giant on Friday appointed its former head coach Antonio Lopez Habas of Spain as the team’s new Technical Director ahead of the upcoming Indian Super League season. Habas returns to India, having previously managed ATK Mohun Bagan during the Hero ISL 2021-22 season. “Along with making a powerful first-team side, Mohun Bagan ... <a title="Antonio Lopez Habas joins Mohun Bagan as Technical Director" class="read-more" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/antonio-lopez-habas-joins-mohun-bagan-as-technical-director/" aria-label="More on Antonio Lopez Habas joins Mohun Bagan as Technical Director">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/antonio-lopez-habas-joins-mohun-bagan-as-technical-director/">Antonio Lopez Habas joins Mohun Bagan as Technical Director</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Mohun Bagan Super Giant on Friday appointed its former head coach Antonio Lopez Habas of Spain as the team’s new Technical Director ahead of the upcoming Indian Super League season.</p>



<p>Habas returns to India, having previously managed ATK Mohun Bagan during the Hero ISL 2021-22 season.</p>



<p>“Along with making a powerful first-team side, Mohun Bagan Super Giant wants to stress on youth development with the aim of producing first-team players from the various age-group sides.</p>



<p>“Habas will be in charge of technical instructions for all the sides. The development side is currently training for the Calcutta League,” the club said in a statement.</p>



<p>The Spaniard is the first head coach to win two Hero ISL titles. He began his journey with Atletico de Kolkata during the 2014 edition and became the first head coach to win the ISL title.</p>



<p>Habas had a stint with FC Pune City later on before returning to India to join ATK FC, leading them to the Hero ISL title during the 2019-20 season.</p>



<p>He took charge of ATK Mohun Bagan the following season and guided them to the ISL final that year. He parted ways with the Mariners midway during the 2021-22 season.</p>



<p>Jamshedpur FC signs Steven Dias as head coach of reserve team Another ISL team Jamshedpur FC has signed former India international Steven Dias as the head coach os its reserve team.</p>



<p>Dias returns to Jamshedpur FC after a successful coaching stint as head coach with Ambernath United Atlanta FC.</p>



<p>Under Dias, Ambernath United reached the final round of the Hero I-League Second Division this year, only narrowly missing out on becoming champions of the I-League Second Division where they needed just a draw against Delhi FC.</p>



<p>He led the club to successive undefeated Mumbai FA Elite Division titles in 2022 and 2023 as well as back-to-back Mumbai Women’s League titles.</p>



<p>He was also the head coach of the Maharashtra Santosh Trophy team, leading them to the final round.</p>



<p>The 39-year-old Dias represented India 51 times between 2004 and 2011, scoring seven goals for the Blue Tigers and even captaining the national team during a glorious career that saw him lift the AFC Challenge Cup in 2008 and play in the 2011 AFC Asian Cup.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu/antonio-lopez-habas-joins-mohun-bagan-as-technical-director/">Antonio Lopez Habas joins Mohun Bagan as Technical Director</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mx.online.mills.edu">MX Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://mx.online.mills.edu/antonio-lopez-habas-joins-mohun-bagan-as-technical-director/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
